Alright we've just completed our two flowers.
They've been clear embossed and then they've been embossed with glassy glaze and now what I'm going to do is I'm going to make a center for each of these flower.
And I'm using the jumbo eyelets in my cropodile and I'm just going to go ahead to the middle of that flower using the 3/16th punch.
Punch it out, and do the same thing with the smaller flower.
Punch that out.
And I'm going to be using the pewter eyelets.
And I'm just going to push down.
And sometimes if you're not lined up quite right if you lay it on its front you can push it down a little bit better.
There's one.
And now the second one.
And just push the chipboard back a little bit if you don't have enough room.
Alright now we're ready to give this another squeeze and finish that eyelet.
Alright.
And then the little one same thing.
Alright now we want to hang this off the wreath so I'm going to need a smaller hole.
I need a 3/16th so I'm going to just poke a hole at the tip of the leaf there and at the tip of the leaf there.
And I'm going to be using some natural hemp twine to tie this on to my wreath.
I chose the natural hemp twine because the wreath that I've chosen is the grapevine wreath and you can see I've embossed and glassy glazed a variety of flowers.
I've attached them with the hemp twine and then I've tied it altogether with the 5/8th wide certainly Sally or gross grain ribbon to make a beautiful wreath that your Mom will be proud to hang on her front door.